The reason why it's there is?
I will protect you!
Don't worry, let's go ahead!
The moon will always come to the moon.
The moon will come to the moon.
Let's look at the moon.
It will be a place to go to the future.
That's why I'll be the same path.
I'll give you a wish.
We are one of them.
We might not be traveling in style,?
but I gotta admit, this sure is handy.
I never thought riding a
fish would be so comfy.
Over here! Over here!
Hey, here it comes! No problem!
Oh, no! It's too high! Get ready!
Watch out! I got it! Oh, man!
Stupid!
This is not your fault!
I was gonna get that one!
I want to play, too!
Ugh.
I didn't think there'd be canals
running by people's houses, too.
They're everywhere.
I'm trying to follow the map, but
I don't want to miss anything.
Huh?
Uh, we're about to go against
the flow, is that okay?
We're not supposed to go up, are we?
What's wrong way?
Go right, right!
Awesome!
You horsefish can swim uphill too?
What can't you do?
Look!
The canals go to the top
of the building! Who cares?
We're going the wrong way!
We need to go to the
shopping district! Why?
What's the rush?
You wanna see the rest
of the city, don't you?
Look, look! Do something! Turn around!
Oh yeah, we're up pretty high, aren't we?
That's not what I want to hear!
Help me!
Stop showing off!
Huh?
Best prices in town. Check us out.
Take a look over here.
I promise you won't regret it.
We're starting our 50 % off sale.
Don't miss it.
We've got rare goods for
the distinguished customer.
Oh, man, check out all the stuff.
We ended up in the shopping
district after all.
Wait, you guys took a
shortcut, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
You're a lot smarter than
I gave you credit for.
This has got to be the
biggest market I've ever seen!
Uh-huh.
Whoa, look!
That bull is huge! Whoa! Should we move?
It's coming straight at us!
That thing is scary!
Pinky eats people?
I wonder if this one is a king.
Huh?
What's with them?
They're all wearing masks!
Wow, neat. They're pretty.
They must be going to a party.
What's up? See something?
Freshly made water water
octopus dumplings for sale.
Three water water croquettes coming up.
I didn't know they sold food.
I'm hungry, let's buy everything!
Wait, go back!
Hey, Lopey, where are you going?
I don't know, ask my ride.
Huh?
Hello there.
How may I help you?
I see, so you were hungry, too.
Water-water meat is the
Yagara's favorite food,
although we usually cook it for humans.
Meat, huh?
I'll take ten, please.
They're so good that the cooks from the
gourmet town come by them in secret.
Bet you never had anything like it, huh?
So soft! Yummy!
Oh, really? They're good?
Let me try one, Luffy.
No way, I'm not sharing.
Nami, he's being mean.
Make him share with me.
More masks.
People all over town are wearing them.
There's something strange about this.
Nami, are you listening?
This is it.
As soon as we take the Watergate elevator,
will be at the Shipbuilding
Island in no time.
What's this Watergate thing?
It's that tower right ahead of us.
Attention, everyone!
The elevator is ready to go.
Bulls and riders, enter now.
Proceed in an orderly fashion, please.
All aboard for Shipbuilding Island?
In downtown Water 7 at this time passengers
should enter the elevator quickly.
The gate will Be closing
in only one minute.
Something crazy is gonna happen!
I just know it!
The gate closed. It's starting!
I see.
First you go in, the gate shuts,
the water fills the elevator, and
then everybody floats to the top.
I still don't get it,
but it sure is awesome.
They really do use water
for everything here.
Hey Who are you calling moss head jerk?
You awake?
Uh-huh You know where Robin went?
She's not on the ship
Oh, I remember.
She said she was going
out with Chopper! What?
They were doing some shopping, I think
What the hell?
Does that mean I'm stuck on
this ship alone with you?
That's gotta be the most
boring thing in the world!
Yep, that's why I'm sleeping.
Fine.
I need to do our grocery
shopping so I'm taking off too.
Take good care of the boat while I'm gone.
Sleep already, huh?
Whatever.
Keep up the good work.
We made it!
So this is the best shipyard
in the whole world, huh?
It's even fancier than
the rest of the town.
They've got a lot more ground to work
with than the residential district,
that's for sure.
Everything's huge! So cool!
Of course it's cool!
This place is the best!
Oh, there's a bunch of people over there.
Think something's going
on at the shipyard?
Let's go check it out!
Go, Yoggana!
Yeah! Whoa!
Whoa, did you see that?
Oh, my God.
Look, over there, it's Luchi!
He's so handsome!
Pauly's here today, too, right?
Who cares about those guys, huh?
Now, Lulu, that's a real man.
Just look at that mustache!
Whatever!
Nobody's manlier than Tile Stone!
Hey, mister!
Hmm?
What's this crowd about? Oh,
it was just some boneheaded pirates trying
to pick a fight with
the shipwrights again.
You know, happens all the time.
But our guys send them
packing like always.
Those pirates will never
learn their lesson.
Whoa, that's nuts!
The shipwrights can beat up pirates?
Ah, you must be tourists, huh?
The shipwrights are, well, hm.
They're like celebrities to us.
In fact, you might say that
this crowd is their fan club.
We're always watching
the Gallylock company.
They're strong, they're skilled,
and they're the pride of
every citizen in Water 7.
Wow, I can't wait to meet them.
Hey, Luffy, let's hurry up and
get the gold traded in, okay?
This is fun, but it can wait till later.
Come on!
It says that we're in the
Backstreet Shopping District.
Seems awfully crowded for a
Backstreet, if you ask me.
Kinda neat that they have
places to walk around, though.
They must have put a lot of
thought into the town's design.
Yeah.
What is that guy selling?
It looks creepy.
It's just a mask shop.
I noticed a lot of people
around town wearing them,
so they must buy them from there.
It's something you wear?
I thought that was their face.
Wow, that's a big relief.
It seems the people here take the
Sea Train to San Faldo Island,
where they hold a costume
carnival every day.
Huh?
How do you know that?
We just got here.
The people walking by
are talking about it.
Whoa.
And do you hear everything they say?
I can't help it.
Ever since I was young,
I've made it a habit to keep a
critical eye and ear on my environment.
Oh.
Wow, Robin.
That's cool.
Huh.
Doctor.
Hmm?
See that?
I think we found your bookstore.
Really?
Can we go inside?
Of course, be my guest.
Today is the best day ever!
Cape.
Hey!
What are you waiting for?
If I'm in my human form,
Um, maybe it'll be okay.
Huh? Why?
What a funny mask.
What's your costume?
Oh, uh, a human reindeer? Hmm.
Well, as long as you're having fun, right?
Hmm.
Oh, hey, wait.
Robin? Robin?
Hello?
Robin?
Pity, I was hoping that we
could kill you in your sleep.
You bastards sure got a lot of nerve.
Who are you?
100 million berries!
Let down, stupid!
You want the whole city to know
how much cash we're lugging around?
You're really gonna give
us that much money, mister?
Play it cool, Luffy.
You gotta handle these
things like a professional.
It may sound like a lot, but that's
most certainly what it's worth.
It has historical value and high purity.
With a hundred million, we can make
the Mary even better than before.
No kidding, and we'll
have plenty to spare.
Then we'll spend the rest on a
big statue to put on the deck.
No, no, we won't.
Well, that's wonderful.
I'm glad you accept the amount.
Now I need your thumbprint
and signature here.
After that, I'll prepare
your money lickety-split.
You can have both my
thumbs if you want them!
Mine too!
The more thumbs, the better, right?
Uh, what's up?
Giving him a tillprint?
Before we sign anything, there
are three things I'd like to say.
Mr. Appraiser.
First, I forgot to mention this, but he's
got a 100 million bounty on his head.
Second, I don't accept
the appraisal you gave us.
Third, if you try to lie to us again,
it'll be the last lie you
ever tell. You got that?
Please forgive me!
300 million?
This is like a dream come true!
Skypiea paid off after all, I
never thought I'd see the day.
You know, I always wanted
to be filthy, right?
It's our money too!
Pleasure doing business with you.
I'm so comfortable having all
this money in one place, guys.
It's scary.
I mean, what if I trip and it
all falls out or something?
That was great.
You sure were scary back there, Nami.
I estimated 300 million from the start,
but I figured he wouldn't give it up easy.
He really got to work on your game face.
Good thing I was there.
Cut it out.
You're making me nervous
swinging that around.
Well, whatever.
We got our money now,
and that's what matters.
You dropped it!
Don't let it fall in the room!
Phew, that would've been bad
if the money got wet, huh?
If you lose my money,
you're playing and flying!
Keep out and cramming down your throat!
I'm sorry, very sorry.
But please, don't break my face anymore.
You don't know who we are? Really?
Because we sure know you, Pirate Hunter.
Babies stop crying when
they hear our name.
A collection of bounty hunters!
We are the Franky family!
Now if you don't mind,
I think we'll be taking that 60
million bounty you've got on your head.
When we're done with you,
we'll wait inside that cabin of yours and
ambush the rest of your
crew when they get back.
We're gonna be rolling
in the dough in no time!
It's my lucky day!
Lucky, huh?
We'll see about that now, won't we? Ah!
Two swords, Tile!
Rhino!
Psycho!
Back to sleep.
Oh, man!
I don't know, Nami.
Maybe we should take the cash
back to the ship after all.
That'd be a complete waste of time.
The shipyard is right around the corner.
Come on, you don't have
to ride so far away.
Let me play with the money.
Anyway, we'll probably head
back to the Mary soon enough.
After we meet with the shipwrights, I'm
sure they'll need to look at the damages?
before they can give us a quote.
I didn't think of it that way.
I guess I could watch the money till then.
I've never carried so much
cash at once, that's all.
I don't know how to handle it.
Well, that's only natural.
Just don't flail it around and throw
it in any rivers and you'll be fine.
Ooh, they're selling
water buns over there.
Let's buy a hundred of them.
Shut up.
How about a thousand?
How about shut up?
Okay.
Right, back to the shipyard.
And it looks like the
crowd's cleared out, too.
Well, that's good.
We have enough to deal with without the
Shipwright fan club getting in the way.
All we gotta do is find that ice guy.
Uh, wait, what's his name again?
It's Iceberg.
Oh, yeah, now I remember Ice Pops.
The old lady back at the train station
said that's who we needed to talk to,
but now that I think about it, we
don't know anything about him, do we?
Well, it's the only lead we've got.
I don't even know how this place works.
Is it okay just to walk in?
That's what I'm doing! Not again!
Hold it right there.
You got a lot of gumption
just waltzing in like that.
Why don't we take a step
over here, then we can talk.
Don't worry, it's not personal.
You're outsiders is all, so you're
not allowed inside the plant.
Oopsy-daisy.
All right, Champ, what brings
you to the docks today?
Come on, Usopp, I know it's you
I'm right here, Loopy! Idiot!
Oh, now that I look at
it, his nose is square.
Anyway, that aside, we came here to
see Iceberg, if that's all right?
Hmm, is that so, little miss?
Are you customers?
Oh, that's nifty.
Not every day that
youngsters come here with
a letter of introduction
from Granny Kokoro!
Uh, hold on, how old are
you? I'm 23. Why do you ask?
You know, for someone who's
hardly any older than us,
you sure do talk like an old man.
I get that a lot.
So do you know Iceberg, or do
we come to the wrong place?
Well, of course I know Iceberg.
Why, I'd say that everyone here knows him,
seeing as he's the mayor
of the city and all.
Wow.
Ice Pops is an important guy, huh?
Darn Skippy he is.
He's also the president of our galley law
company and manager of the
C-train on top of that.
I didn't know he was such a big deal.
I had a feeling you
weren't from around here.
Iceberg is pretty famous in these parts.
But do you know where we can find him?
Hmm, that's the question, isn't it?
He keeps pretty busy, of course.
Hunting him down can be a chore sometimes.
But you work for him, right?
Can't you get in touch somehow?
I suppose I could, but it seems like
you're in a hurry to get this done.
Not exactly, but...
It's fine, I understand.
You're richin' to have
your ship looked at, right?
Where did you anchor it?
Uh, it's over by the rocky cape.
Alrighty then, I'll skedaddle
over there real quick.
If I take a gander at
your ship beforehand,
you can start talking cost
with Iceberg right away.
As I said, he's very busy, so I'm
sure he'll be grateful as well.
Wait, skedaddle like how?
On a yagata or what?
I thought we were trying to save time.
If you folks can hang
tight for 10 minutes,
I should be back in two
shakes of a lamb's tail.
Just 10 minutes?
That's right, or your money back.
Whoa!
He's fast!
He flew!
Wait, where's he going?
If he jumps off the edge, he'll fall!
Whoa! Come back!
So cool yeah but is he gonna be okay?
Don't worry he's always
soaring through town!
Huh they call him the mountain
wind if you didn't know
he's the galley law company's
doc one carpentry foreman kaku
I see.
So this is the city of water, huh?
Pretty impressive place.
Lives up to its name, that's for sure.
I mean, look around.
Clean water, clean streets, fresh food,
and most importantly, plenty of cute girls.
This place has it all.
Take my word for it,
this is the perfect place to take that
special someone on a romantic stroll.
But why stop at one when
I have two lovely ladies?
This one is Nami, and
this one here is Robin.
You're scaring away the customers.
Stop making that creepy face and tell me
which water water cabbage you want already.
I'll take both of them.
Oh, and there was something
I wanted to ask you.
I'm looking for some local specialties
that are in season right now.
So what have you got? Let's see.
This way?
This place sure is a pain
when you have to walk.
If I don't stop running into dead ends and
start figuring out where the hell I am,
this food's going to go bad
before I make it back to the Mary.
Don't tell me Zorro's brain fungus
is starting to spread to me too.
Robin, boy, am I glad to see you!
It's me, Sanji! Yoo-hoo!
Robin, look!
She disappeared.
Looks like another dead end to me.
The only way to go is up, but there's...
Usopp?
Man, I don't know what's
up with this place.
I'm not going crazy, am I?
Well, Lock here.
That must be the one.
Pardon me.
Well, it's just your sub.
My goodness.
I know they told me their
ship needed repairs,
but I didn't think it
would be in shambles.
We should start by replacing this mast.
Wait, that's not right.
Hey, I see you! Don't move! You hear me?
Oh, pardon.
I didn't intend to disturb your nap.
Jeez, that was a big surprise.
I've never seen someone
jump that far before.
Well, my craftsmen are the best
in the business for a reason.
Who is this guy? Don't ask me.
Extraordinary ships are not born
from ordinary circumstances.
They require a nearly
superhuman level of skill.
By the way, Clover...
I've already finished
the background check.
The one in the middle is Straw Hat Luffy.
His crew also includes Pirate
Hunter Zoro and Nico Robin.
Their combined bounty is 239 million.
They have four other members
without posted bounties,
and their crew was
formed in the East Blue.
Named after their captain, they're
known simply as the Straw Hat Pirates.
They've really got our
number! I see. Welcome.
My name is Iceberg.
I'm the boss here.
And this is a mouse I just picked up.
Its name is, let's see, Tyrannosaurus.
I'll need some rodent food in a cage.
I've already taken care of that, sir.
Well, amazing work, Carly Fire.
Just doing my job.
Speaking of which,
you're due at a hotel in Chess for lunch
with a glassware factory executive.
After that, you're set to make
a speech at Liguria Square.
And once that's finished,
you'll be meeting with Mr.
Bimini, the mayor of Pucci.
Their local newspaper is scheduled
to interview you as well.
Oh, and when you return to the office,
there's a folder full of important documents?
I need your signature on.
I don't wanna.
Very well, then I'll
cancel everything for you.
Hold on, you're not serious, are you?
What's the point of having power
if I don't get to do what I want?
If that's how you run things, you
gotta be the worst mayor in the world.
Yeah, Pops, that's pretty lazy.
So, hold on, are you sure this is the
guy that old lady was talking about?
Uh-huh, he's the guy, all right.
How dare you!
What's the big idea, lady?
That was scary.
I won't stand here and
let you insolent louts
disrespect one of the world's
leading ship engineers.
Hey, what's going on over there?
Iceberg's secretary just flipped
out on some pirates again.
I wish she'd flip out on me.
Pardon me.
I get a bit carried
away from time to time.
Still, Iceberg is a respected figure here
in Water 7, so try to show some courtesy.
Yes, please don't provoke Kalifa.
When she lashes out in
anger, her brain sucks.
We might have hurt his
feelings, but you hurt his face!
You're way meaner than us!
Putting all that behind us, if you're
Iceberg, you're the man we're looking for.
Here, we brought a letter of
introduction for you to look at.
From Granny Kokoro?
Oh, take a look at their ship, it says.
What? Are you serious?
There has to be something we
can do to change your mind.
If money's the issue, we can pay.
If you're really the best, then you've
got to be the one to fix our Mary.
Come on, we're begging.
Okay. That's it?
You don't need to think about it?
Nope.
Hey, why did you tear up the letter?
The lipstick mark was creeping me out.
Even so, Granny Kokoro and I have
been drinking buddies for years.
Well,
and since Kaku has already gone
to make an assessment for me,
it would seem like a waste
to turn you down now,
wouldn't you say?
Besides, it's not like I
had anything better to do.
Let me show you around the factory.
Sound good?
Sweet! Bring it on!
Come along with me, then.
Did he seriously cancel all of his
meetings just to give us a tour?
Yeah!
You gotta let me sit on
all the cool ships, okay?
Oh, right. The money.
Wait, what? No!
Hey, what's wrong, Usopp?
Come on.
The money, it disappeared.
Did she drop it somewhere?
I don't know.
Hey, over there!
Wait who are you?
Why are you taking your money?
I mean, give it back.
We need it. You jerks!
Do you hear me?
Thanks for the cash!
Give us our money back!